Ying-Ying Szeto

yingyingszetoo@gmail.com +1 (646) 421 3288 LinkedIn @yingyingszeto

PORTFOLIO

yingyingszeto.github.io/portfolio

EDUCATION

User Experience Design

Master • Falmouth University Falmouth, UK

Visual and Digital Art

Diploma • Humber College Toronto, ON, Canada

SKILLS

Design

UX Strategy

User Research

Interaction Design

Wireframing

Prototyping

Usability Testing

Visual Design

Tools

Figma

Miro

Mural

Optimal Workshop

HTML/CSS/JS

JIRA

LANGUAGE

English

Chinese

SUMMARY

UX / Product Designer with over 5+ years of experience. I specialize in end-to-end product design, user research, and concept development. I've shaped Enterprise B2B and SaaS products across industries including insurance, customer communication software, and automotive marketplace. I am authorized to work in the US; no sponsorship required.

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer Manulife @Keyteo Consulting

B2B • Insurance

- Led end-to-end design for several SaaS applications from concept to completion, impacting 50k+ agents across Hong Kong, Vietnam, the Philippines, Indonesia, and Malaysia.
- Partnered closely with cross-functional teams across the entire product lifecycle including Product Managers, Engineers, Operations, and Organizational Leaders.
- Leveraged and enhanced internal design systems to drive consistency in product ecosystem.

UX/UI Designer maaiiConnect

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020 • Hong Kong

Mar 2021 - Aug 2023 • *Hong Kong*

B2B SaaS • Customer Support

- Transformed the onboarding experience for B2B products through a simple and delightful design to guide chatbot installation, reducing customer inquiry tickets by 30% in 2 months.
- Collaborated with engineers and QAs to push for pixel-perfect production matching the design.

UX/UI Designer EAB Systems

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 • Hong Kong

B2B SaaS • Insurance

- Designed and customized user flows and design for client AXA based on the core SaaS product.
- Developed design concepts and pitched them to clients from various insurance enterprises.

Web Designer

Nov 2015 - Apr 2017 • Toronto, ON, Canada

autoTrader.ca

B2C • Automotive marketplace

• Collaborated with the UX and development teams to improve marketplace design and create creative graphics.

Freelance Designer

2013 - Present

 Designed and developed websites for New Era Cap, Glo, Yuki Spa, and small businesses in Canada and Hong Kong.